Finding Aid for the Hilda Kuper Papers LSC.1343
UCLA Library Special Collections
- King's speeches., 1968. (Box 47, Folder 4)
- King's speeches., 1969. (Box 47, Folder 5)
- King's speeches., 1971. (Box 47, Folder 6)
- King's speeches., 1972. (Box 47, Folder 7)
- King's speeches., 1973. (Box 47, Folder 8)
- King's speeches., 1974. (Box 47, Folder 9)
- References, chapter 2. (Box 47, Folder 10)
- References, chapter 3. (Box 47, Folder 11)
- References, chapter 4. (Box 47, Folder 12)
- References, chapter 5. (Box 47, Folder 13)
- References, chapter 6. (Box 47, Folder 14)
- References, chapter 11. (Box 47, Folder 15)
- References, chapter 12. (Box 47, Folder 16)
- References, chapter 15. (Box 47, Folder 17)
- 1972-1974. (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Clippings., 1973. (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Clippings., 1975. (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Photos for biography. (Box 47, Folder 21)
- O.A.U. and Swazi foreign affairs. (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Case to Privy Council. (Box 47, Folder 23)
- King's petition. (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Women--Wisconsin. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- --NB., 1968 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Road to independence. (Box 48, Folder 3)
- King's speeches., 1970. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Kingship cases. & customs., 1956 1967-1968. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Mnt. Madeuu Deamini. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- 1966. (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Notarial deeds and leases. (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Cyclone Domoina., 1984. (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Swaziland National Center. (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Clans--Swaziland. (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Spicer. (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Chiefs. (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Regiments. (Box 48, Folder 14)
- First election--Sobhuza forms political party. (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Swazi government. (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Philip Bonner. (Box 48, Folder 17)
- 1963. (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Minerals. (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Succession. (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Swazi reports. (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Chiefs. (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Visit to Swaziland., 1966. (Box 49, Folder 4)
- History. (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Incwala Msimanga. (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Material chapter 14., 1964. (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Regiments. (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Chapter 13 additional material. (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Swazi independence--old version of history. (Box 49, Folder 10)
- A witch in my heart & other stories. (Box 49, Folder 11)
- National Science Foundation application., 1986. (Box 49, Folder 12)
- 1973. (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Biography--miscellaneous material. (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Colin Legum. (Box 49, Folder 15)
- 1965. (Box 49, Folder 16)
- 1972. (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Incwala. (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Clan names. (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Amos Zwane. (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Edward Hower. (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Historical documents. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 1970. (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Tibongo. (Box 50, Folder 7)
- 1984. (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Tibongo., 1970. (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Talk. (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Games. (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Letters from Swaziland. (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Kinship. (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Urbanization--Swaziland. (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Cattle. (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Swazi--Western education. (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Anthropology notes. (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Political--succession & inheritance. (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Political--Incwala. (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Political--slavery. (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Political--traditional, councils, miscellaneous. (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Political--traditional, chiefs, indians, etc. (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Political--traditional. (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Political--Western administration. (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Political--history of Western administration. (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Political--history of Swazi people. (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Political--Swaziland & South Africa. (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Economics. (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Occupation & technology. (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Land tenure, etc. (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Land--agriculture. (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Land--livestock. (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Land--food. (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Locations. (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Swazi correspondence. (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Tibongo. (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Chapter 11 additional material. (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Swazi students in America. (Box 52, Folder 5)
- African correspondence., 1980s. (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Correspondence., 1970s-1980s. (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Swaziland Peace Corps. (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Swaziland., 1970. (Box 52, Folder 9)
- World book. (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Cohen, David. (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Duckworth. (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Essays on independence., [2 folders.] (Box 52, Folder 13-14)
- Swazi law [orban]. (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Pierre Van den Berghe. (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Peace Corps lang. (Box 52, Folder 17)
- A. Richards & Vic Turner. (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Receipts--Swaziland., 1986. (Box 53, Folder 1)
- King's correspondence--Sobhuza II & Matsebula. (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Calendars. (Box 53, Folder 3)
- B. Rosen-Prinz. (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Beth Ph.D. (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Swazi animal and plants. (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Postscript--Duckworth. (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Moore letter. (Box 53, Folder 8)
- HK--personal (Featherstone's letter). (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Publications re Swaziland independence., 1968-1969. (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Publications re coronation of Makhosetive., 1986. (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Royal villages of Swaziland. (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Politics--party. (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Economics. (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Land. (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Education. (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Law. (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Swaziland Legislative Council. (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Drawings. (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Health. (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Events--chronology. (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Language & custom. (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Census. (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Research notes. (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Swaziland phone book., 1981. (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Swaziland constitution., 1970. (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Crown Prince Makhosetive--pictorial biography. (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Maps--genealogy. (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Photographs. (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Printed material re Swaziland. (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Photographs and printed material. (Box 56)
  Scope and Contents
  This box contains photographs that were used in Hilda Kuper's book, The Swazi.
- Education scrapbook. (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Essay papers scrapbook. (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Political ledger. (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Economic ledger. (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Pondo women--photographs. (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Photographs., 1967. (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Photographs--Zimbabwe., 1929. (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Photographs., August 9, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Photographs., June 1978. (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Photographs--Mhlanga., September 2-3, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 5, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 7, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 8, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 10, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 13, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Photographs--Swaziland, graduation., September 14-15, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 16, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 17, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 21, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Photographs--views of Swaziland., [2 folders.] (Box 58, Folder 16-17)
- Photographs--Swaziland, Mbaban Bank and interview for SBC., September 14, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Photographs--Swaziland., 1936. (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Photographs--maps of Swaziland. (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Photographs--Hilda Kuper's family. (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Photographs--Fellows & staff, Center for Advanced Studies in the Behavioral Sciences., 1976-1977. (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Photographs--Swaziland., September 9, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Photographs--Swaziland, royal ceremony. (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Slides--Swaziland. (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Slides--London. (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Negatives. (Box 58, Folder 27)
  Nitrate negatives of Swaziland from this folder have been removed to storage in the UCLA nitrate vault.
- Color negatives of Swaziland. (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Correspondence--Miscellaneous cards, postcards, and letters (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Recognitions awarded to Kuper. (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Curriculum vitae--updated copies and drafts. (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Listing of books kept in Kuper's office. (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Christmas cards and birthday cards. (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Christmas cards and birthday cards. (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Printed material. (Box 59, Folder 8)
- New York University. (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Photographs. (Box 59, Folder 10)
- From water well to tribal center. (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Ecuador. (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Photographs of Swaziland on loose pages. (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Loose black and white Photographs--Swaziland. (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Color Photographs--Swaziland. (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Photographs of Johannesburg. (Box 60, Folder 4)
- On the road from Johannesburg to Swaziland., 1937. (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Photos of Swaziland., 1930s. (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Various photos of Swaziland selected for slides. (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Transkei., 1937. (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Photos of Swaziland., 1930s; [2 folders.] (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
- Swaziland. --nitrate negatives., 1930s (Box 60, Folder 11)
  These items have been removed and are stored in UCLA's nitrate storage vault.
- Good negatives., color., 1970s (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Inserts--photocopies of photographs. (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Counsellor award given to Kuper by King Sobhuza II on with letter of response., September 4, 1981 (Box 61)
- 2 Photograph albums of Swaziland. (Box 61)
- Black and white negatives of Swaziland. (Box 62)
- Black and white prints of Swaziland. (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Color negatives of Swaziland. (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Photo album of Swaziland. (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Nitrate negatives of Swaziland. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  These have been removed to storage in the UCLA nitrate box.
- Notebooks, 1966-69.; --Field notes, personal notes, etc. and one folder of loose items found with notebooks. (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Appointment books and calendars., 1966-1990. (Box 64)
- The Swaziland Student newsletter. (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Issues of --Newsletter of the Swaziland Democratic Party., September 12, 1962-March 11, 1963; (Incomplete). (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Four full issues of Umbiki., 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  In Swazi and English.
- Issues of The Times of Swaziland & The Swazi Observer., 1979, 1982, 1989, & 1990. (Box 64, Folder 4)
- January 16, 1984 issue of Time Magazine; Focus on Africa. (Box 64, Folder 5)
- AME Swaziland choir., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Secrecy., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Swazi music for military band--cassette tape--played by the band of the Royal Artillery. (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Swazi Religion., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 4)
- African liberation day--take one., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Secrecy 12/17., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Power of secrecy., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Meeting at Lobamba, Natal rebellion, subpoena on p.c., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Mandela release. --radio & television, Sunday afternoon/evening., February 11, 1990; Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Trial of Bunu's widows, education of Sobhuza., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Hilda--conversations and lecture., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 11)
- P.M. Taiwan., June 12, 1976; Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Review of Genocide by Leo Kuper., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Ngwenga., July 1972.; Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Secrecy., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Various letters and interviews with Sishay Nxumclo and Princess Nergwan., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 16)
- An address by Hilda Kuper., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Unlabeled cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Lobamba. --candidate for imbok and king's speech., March 27, 1972; Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Q72., Cassette tape. (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Issues and articles in Swazi newspapers celebrating King Sobhuza's 80th & 81st birthdays., 1979-1980. (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Newsletter--News from Swaziland., May 21, 1984- December 15, 1985. (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Newsletter--News from Swaziland., January 2-December 1, 1986. (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Newsletter--News from Swaziland., January 5-November 9, 1987. (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Newsletter--News from Swaziland., March 14-November 21, 1988. (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Newsletter--News from Swaziland., January 3-October 16, 1989. (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Newspapers and clippings announcing the death of King Sobhuza II, August-September 1982. (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Clippings from various Southern African newspapers about Swaziland, July-September 1987. (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Clippings from various Southern African newspapers about Swaziland, June-December 1989. (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Clippings from various Southern African newspapers about Swaziland, March-April 1991. (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Clippings from various Southern African newspapers about Swaziland., undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Newspaper clippings from The Los Angeles Times and New York Times on Rhodesia and Ian Smith., February 1979. (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Clippings from newspapers about Southern Africa--Miscellaneous., 1984-1990. (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Clippings on investigation of Winnie Mandela and release of Nelson Mandela., February 1984 February 1990. (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Clippings on Sir Seretse Khama'd illness and death., July 1980. (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Clippings about minority cultures--Tibetans, Hungarians, and Brazilian native peoples. (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous--Brochures, pamphlets, programmes, articles, etc.; mostly on Swaziland. (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Reports, projects, plans, and studies on Swaziland land and migration., 1965-1979.; 8 printed items. (Box 67)
- Index of reports and papers on Southern African rural development areas. (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Paper: Customary Land Tenure and Modern Agriculture on Swazi Nation Land., 1971. (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Draft report on the living conditions of women in the North Rural Development Area of Swaziland., 1977. (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Part of paper: Part A Electricity from Mini-Hydro for Rural Water Supply Systems., undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Lecture notes--Land Tenure: It's Influence on Economic and General Human Welfare., March 15, 1976. (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Paper: Perceptions and attitudes of rural householders in the Northern RDA., undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Report on the first round of demographic survey, Swaziland., 1975. (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Resolutions., October 26, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  First page in English, succeeding pages in Swazi.
- Paper: Swaziland Renewable Energy Project, by Thomas Graham., September 3, 1979. (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Working paper: Migrant Labour and Rural Homesteads, by Rosen-Prinz and Prinz., September 1978. (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Emeriti program., 1984 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  --Letter noting HK's selection as Charter fellow, listing of names, newsletter.
- Material regarding participation in the Faculty Women's Club. (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Letter of nomination for Distinguished Faculty Seminar., 1987. (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research--Material regarding conference in Austria., 1977. (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Honorary degree from the University of Swaziland., September 15, 1990. (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Unfinished articles and tasks--Notes, papers, and articles. (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Photocopied pictures of Swaziland and King Sobhuza. (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Notes and drafts of chapters. (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Papers and articles by various authors. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  --some possibly used by Kuper, others as gifts from friends.
- Framed certificate of Swazi citizenship., July 16, 1970. (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Two reels microfilm: (A) African Arts vol.12, no.1-4 Index () and (B) African Arts vol.14, no.1-4 (, 1978-79 1980-81). (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Personal copy of Sobhuza II with corrections and annotations. (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Notecards of unknown content. (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Folder packet: Academic Specialist Program of USIA. (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Folder packet: University of Swaziland graduation ceremony programme., 1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Folder packet: Welcome to Swaziland. (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Manuscripts and editor's review of Kuper's play The Decision. (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Publishing firms. regarding various items written by Kuper., 1978-1991 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- UNESCO reports on indigenous peoples. (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Amnesty International--newsletters and correspondence.; clippings., December 1984-January 1986 1981. (Box 69, Folder 9)
- CONAIE - Notes, papers, clippings on Ecuadorian and Cambodian peoples and environmental issues. (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Clippings--Regarding indigenous tribes of South and Central America. (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Notes--5 legal size notepads with notes of unknown content and dates. (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: African Studies Association., 1978. (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Personal correspondence: Dorothy Woodson., 1989-1990. (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Papers and correspondence regarding U.S. Citizenship., 1979. (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: International African Institute., 1978-1985. (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Correspondence and writings: Carole Allen., January 1970. (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and writings: Rohit Barot., August 1969. (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Social Science Research Council Application and correspondence re: grant for Swazi research., 1968-1971. (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Corrinne Armstrong., 1964-1979. (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Correspondence and writings: Dawn Chatty., 1980-1990. (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: University of Swaziland, regarding a joint affiliation with UCLA., 1986-1987. (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Correspondence regarding permission rights / use of Kuper's works by others. (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Margo Russell., 1990. (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Work of Stephen Coddington., undated; Part handwritten on legal sheets, part typed. (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Papers by Huw Jones--Pre-colonial distribution of Swazi peoples. (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Works of Meyer Fortes--Mystical, Superstitious, and Religious Practices of African peoples. (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Writings by Mike G. Smith--Central Nigeria. (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Writings by Edward A. Alpers--Iron age Mozambique. (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Article by Lionel Gossman: The Signs of the Theater. (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Works by Robert Gordon on Namibia with other related items. (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Works by Marilyn Ravicz on art related issues. (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Articles by and about James Freeman. (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences., 1972-1978 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  (Kuper was a fellow).
- National Science Fund budget proposals and extensions for Kuper's research in Swaziland., 1966-1971. (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Karen Tranberg Hansen., 1981. (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Book reviews on and by H. Kuper. (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Paper: The Ethnic Identity of Sudanese Nubians, by Sondra Hale., 1979. (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Records of donations made to UCLA. (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Materials labeled by Kuper as Self. (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Course materials for destruction and survival of indigenous societies (Anthropology 162P). (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous course materials--photocopies, pictures, etc., not all relating to Kuper. (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Materials for paper given at Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses and Power. Conference., April 1991. (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Statistics on Africa and Swazi diet. (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Invitation to The Joint Committee on Foreign Relations., 1975. (Box 72, Folder 3)
- International College Tutorial Records. and article by Marolyn Ekdahl Ravicz., 1984-85 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- International Conference on the status of women., 1975. (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Materials by the Democratic Socialists of America. (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Receipts and expenses sheets for NSF grant., 1970-1971. (Box 72, Folder 7)
- General notes on genocide., undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
- New cities, urbanism and migration, notepad. (Box 72, Folder 9)
- The Invasion of America., Outline and 2 articles. (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Survival International Newsletters and related clippings. (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Interdisciplinary Committee for the rights of indigenous peoples--flyers, papers, notes. (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Research for destruction and survival of indigenous peoples; course and paper. (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Notes on South African and South American indigenous peoples. (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Reviews and notes of documentary films. (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Photographs and negatives of jewelry. (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Field notebooks of anthropological research in Swaziland and South Africa, 1931-1935 (Box 73)
- Field notebooks of anthropological research in Swaziland and South Africa, 1935-1936 (Box 74)
- Field notebooks of anthropological research in Swaziland and South Africa, 1936-1941 (Box 75)
- Field notebooks of anthropological research in Swaziland and South Africa, 1965-1967 (Box 76)
- Field notebooks of anthropological research in Swaziland and South Africa, 1967-1972 (Box 77)
- Field notebooks of anthropological research in Swaziland and South Africa, 1973-1985 (Box 78)